panlasangpinoy.com 2011-06-23

# Privacy Policy | Panlasang Pinoy

You are here: [Home](http://panlasangpinoy.com/) / Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting PanlasangPinoy.com. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

Note: the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this web site only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.

 **Collection of Information**

We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill you specific request. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example to add you to one of our mailing lists.

 **Slide Guestbook**

The guestbook uses [Slide ](http://www.slide.com/)application. Any information sent through it goes directly to Slide’s database and panlasangpinoy.com has no control of whatsoever on those information sent. Before signing the guestbook, make sure to read Slide’s [Privacy Policy.](http://www.slide.com/static/privacy)

 **Cookie/Tracking Technology**

The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.

 **Google Advertising Cookie**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.  
Because publisher sites and laws across countries vary, we’re unable to suggest specific privacy policy language. However, you may wish to review resources such as the Network Advertising Initiative, or NAI, which suggests the following language for data collection of non-personally identifying information:

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

 **Commitment to Data Security**

Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.

 **Privacy Contact Information**

If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:

By e-mail: webmaster {at} panlasangpinoy {dot} com

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.
